This is pretty much what's happened so far.
到目前為止大概是這樣子…
Ross was in love with Rachel since forever.
打從一開始羅斯就愛瑞秋
Every time he tried to tell her, something got in the way...
但每次他想要表白 總是會遇上阻礙…
...Iike cats,Italian guys.
像是貓咪，意大利佬
And finally,Chandler was, like,"Forget about her."
最後錢德勸他死心
When Ross was in China,Chandler let it slip that Ross loved Rachel.
羅斯去中國考古時 錢德說漏嘴羅斯愛瑞秋
She was,like,"Oh,my God!"
瑞秋非常驚訝
So she went to the airport to meet him.
於是她到機場接羅斯
She didn 't know Ross was getting off the plane with another woman.
她不知道羅斯 帶了另一個女人下飛機
That's pretty much everything you need to know.
大概就是這樣子了
But enough about us. How have you been?
說夠了我們，你們近來如何？
The One With Ross' New Girlfriend
六人行 第2季 第01集 羅斯的新女友
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
從北京飛來第457號班機 已經降落
Oh,my God!
我的天啊！
天啊！
Excuse me.
對不起
Move,move,move! Emergency,please!
借過，借過！ 緊急事件，拜託！
Excuse me,excuse me.
對不起，對不起
There you are!
原來你們在那裡！
So,so....
所以，所以…
How was China? You!
中國怎麼樣？老兄！
It was great.
很棒…
What happened?
你怎麼啦？
-You're bleeding. -I am?
你在流血 是嗎？
Oh,look at that! Yes,I am.
啊，怪怪！我是在流血
Enough about me, Mr. Back From The Orient!
別管我了 周遊東方的旅人！
Come on,I wanna hear everything! Everything!
我要聽一切事情！ 什麼都不要漏掉！
Well,where do I start?
嗯，要從何開始？
This is Julie. Julie,this is Rachel.
這位是茱莉 茱莉，這位是瑞秋
These are....
這些…
...aren't for you.
…不是要給你的
These are for you.
這些是要送給你的
Welcome to our country.
歡迎光臨敝國
Thank you. I'm from New York.
謝謝，我是紐約人
No problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
沒關係，我用它來止血
Baggage claim?
去拿行李？
I'm telling U.She went to the airport, and she's gonna go for it with Ross.
她去了機場 準備跟羅斯坦白了
Oh,my God! This is huge!
天啊！這是大事！
This is bigger than huge. This is....
這比大事還大 這是…
All right,what's bigger than huge?
什麼比大事還大？
This?
這件事嗎？
Guys,you got new haircuts!
喂，你們剪頭髮了！
Yes,we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
是的，謝謝布菲美發大師
Because,you know,"lf you don't look good,we don't look good."
因為如果你們丟臉 我們也丟臉（廣告詞）
I love that voice!
我喜歡這聲音！
And the winner is Eva Godna!
Airport. Airport. Ross.
機場…機場…羅斯
Not alone.
不是一個人
Julie.
茱莉
Arm around her!
摟著她！
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
抽筋！抽筋！
I think she's trying to tell us something.
她好像想說什麼
Quick,get the verbs.
趕快猜動詞
You! You!
你！你！
You said he liked me!
你說他喜歡我！
You!
你！
You slowpokes!
你這個慢郎中！
That's all right. We got the bags.
沒關係，我們拿了行李
This is my sister,Monica.
這是我妹妹摩妮卡
This is Chandler.
這是錢德
Phoebe,hi.
菲比，嗨
Joey.
喬伊
Everyone,this is Julie.
各位，這位是茱莉
Julie.
茱莉
But I'm not here, you haven't met me.
但我還沒到 我們還沒見面
I'll make a better impression when I don't have 20 hours of plane on me.
沒有連坐二十小時飛機 明天我會讓各位刮目相看
-And bus. -Oh,my God!
還有巴士 喔，天啊！
-With the screaming guy -And the spitting.
那個尖叫的傢伙… 還有吐口水
You gotta hear this story.
你們一定要聽這個故事
We're on this bus that's 200 years old.
我們坐的巴士一定有兩百年舊
Two hundred,at least.
至少兩百年舊
And the chicken poops in her lap!
一隻雞拉屎在她腿上！
I'm so sorry.
對不起
I just gave away the ending,didn't l?
我說出了結尾，對不對？
I just heard this story in the cab... and it is all I can think about.
我在計程車上聽了這個故事… 滿腦子想的都是這個
This is amazing.
真是驚人
How did this happen?
怎麼發生的？
We were in grad school together.
羅斯與我一起上過研究所
We haven't seen each other since then. I land in China...
後來就沒有再見面 我降落在中國機場時…
...guess who's in charge of the dig?
…猜猜是誰負責探勘？
Julie!
就是茱莉！
Isn't that great?
真是太棒了！
Isn't that just kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
真是棒得面紅耳赤！ 棒得有苦說不出！
It's an expression.
她習慣這麼說
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
我們只是來打個招呼
-Then we'll see the baby. -Then get some sleep.
然後我們要去看寶寶 然後睡一下覺
It's 6:00 tomorrow night,our time.
現在是中國的明天晚上六點
Don't tell us what's gonna happen. I like being surprised.
別告訴我會發生什麼事 我比較喜歡驚喜
Bye!
再見！
-Can I get some coffee? -Sure.
瑞秋，我想喝點咖啡 沒問題
-Did you talk to him yet? -No.
你跟他談了嗎？ 沒有
Then,no.
沒咖啡給你
What the hell happened to you in China?
你在中國發生了什麼事？
When last we left you, you were in love with,you know.
你離開前還瘋狂愛著… 你知道的
I know I was.
我知道我愛她
But there was always this voice inside that kept saying:
但我心中有這個小聲音告訴我
"It's never gonna happen. Move on." You know whose voice that was?
不可能成功的，死心吧 你知道那是誰的聲音嗎？
God?
上帝？
It was you,pal.
是你的聲音，老哥
Maybe it was God doing me.
也許是上帝模仿我的聲音
You were right. She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
你說得對 她眼中只把我當成朋友
And then I met Julie...
然後我遇見了茱莉
...and we're having a great time.
我們在一起非常開心
I never would have gone for it, if it hadn't been for you.
要不是因為你 我絕不會跟茱莉在一起
Well,you owe me one,big guy.
你欠我一個情，大個兒
Your lemonade.
你的檸檬汁
I didn't order it.
我沒有叫檸檬汁
Then go take that back. They'll charge you for that.
那你最好送回去 否則他們會要你付錢！
Go,go,go! Come on,come on!
快！快！快去！
So what did you find out?
你問出了什麼？
He said....
他說…
They're having a great time.
他們在一起很開心
I'm sorry.
對不起
But the silver lining, if you wanna see it...
但有好的一面 如果你願意這麼看…
...is that he made this decision all by himself...
他完全是自己做了這個決定
...without any outside help whatsoever.
完全沒有受外人的影響
How is that a silver lining?
這怎麼是好的一面？
You have to really wanna see it.
你要非常願意才看得出來
Ironically,these guys were picked last in gym.
諷刺的是這些傢伙 上體育課時沒人願意跟他一隊
Hey,Pheebs.
菲比
You know what I'm thinking?
你知道我想什麼嗎？
How...
因為…
...it's been so long since you've had sex...
你太久沒做愛了…
...you're wondering if they've changed it?
你不知道有沒有什麼改變？
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
不是 但是我現在是這麼想了
So what were you thinking?
你本來在想什麼？
You gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you'd like to do mine.
你幫他們剪頭髮 我想你也應該幫我剪
No.
不要
Why not?
為什麼不要？
Because I'm just....
因為我是個…
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
我非常挑剔 而且有控制狂
No,you're not.
不，你才不是
I know I'm not,but you are.
我知道我不是 不過你是
I was trying to spare your feelings.
我只是不想傷害你的心
Hold on.
請等一下
Ross,Julie for you.
羅斯，茱莉找你
Anybody know a good tailor?
誰能介紹一個好裁縫？
You need clothes altered?
需要改衣服嗎？
No,I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
不，我只是要找一個人 用粉筆在我身上畫線
Go see Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
去找法蘭基 我家人都找他做衣服
He did my first suit when I was 1 5.
我十五歲第一套西裝 就是他做的
No,wait,1 6.
不，十六歲
No,excuse me,1 5.
不，對不起，是十五歲
All right,when was 1 990?
1990年是幾歲？
You have to stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance!
當你掏耳朵時 碰到東西就要停下來！
Sweetheart,I'll see you later.
甜心，待會見
Okay,bye.
好，再見
That is so sweet.
你真好
Okay. No,you hang up.
好，不，你先掛
No,you
不，你先…
One,two,three.
一，二，三
You didn't hang up either.
你也沒有掛
She didn't hang up.
她沒掛
No,you hang up.
不，你掛電話
You. You.
你掛，你掛
Sorry,I thought you were talking to me.
對不起，我以為你在跟我說話
Rachel.
瑞秋！
I'll just call her back.
我打回去
Hi,sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
嗨，甜心，對不起 我們被中斷了
How did this happen to me?
我到底是怎麼回事？
A week ago,two weeks ago,I was fine.
一周前，兩周前，我很好
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
羅斯只是羅斯 這是這個傢伙
Now all of a sudden,he's Ross...
現在突然間，他不一樣了
...this really great guy that I can't have.
變成這個大帥哥 我卻無法得到
Sweetie,I wanted you to have him too.
甜心，我也希望你能得到他
I know you did.
我知道你的心意
I'm just gonna deal with it.
我必須要想辦法
I gotta get out of here!
我必須要離開這裡！
I don't care what you guys say, something's bothering her.
我不管你們怎麼說 她有心事
You know,I think I was 1 6.
我想我是十六歲
Please,just a little bit off the back.
求求你，只要剪後面一點點
I'm still on "no."
我還是堅持不要
Morning.
早安
Could you close your eyes for a sec?
你們能不能閉上眼睛一秒鐘？
No,no,no. I'm not falling for that again.
不，不，不 我可不要再上當
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
昨晚我做了一件蠢事
What stupid thing did you do?
你做了什麼蠢事？
Why don't you just go get dressed...
你為什麼不穿上衣服…
...then you'll be on your way. Bye-bye.
然後就可以走了，再見
How did this happen?
怎麼發生的？
I kind of ran into him last night.
我昨晚湊巧碰到他
-Where? -At his apartment.
在哪裡碰到他？ 在他的公寓
Is this juice?
這是果汁嗎？
And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
你忘了他勾引菲比 所以你才甩了他？
Oh,God,I know. I'm pathetic,I'm a loser.
天啊，我真是可悲 我是個爛貨！
Honey,you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
甜心，你不可悲 你只是傷心
People do stupid things when they're upset.
大家傷心時都會幹蠢事
My God,if I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't
But this is about your horrible mistake.
但這是關於你的大錯誤
Sorry we're late.
對不起，我們遲到了
We were....
我們…
Well,there was touching.
發生過接觸
Hey,Ross!
嗨，羅斯
What a....
真是…
What are you doing here?
你在這裡幹什麼？
I do Raquel!
跟瑞秋嘿咻！
So he's back?
他回來了？
Yeah,he's back. Is that a problem?
對，他回來了 有什麼問題嗎？
No,not a problem.
沒問題
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
很好，沒有問題
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
你不能再碰我的屁股！
Despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension...
儘管有美味的麵包 與濃厚的緊張氣氛…
... my pants need to be altered.
我要去改褲子了
When you see Frankie, tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
你見到法蘭基時 替我問個好
He'll know what it means.
他會明白我的意思
You sure he'll crack that code?
你確定他能解得開密碼嗎？
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here,my hair was so much cuter.
上次波洛來這裡時 我的短髮要可愛多了
All right.
好吧
But you have to promise that you will not be all controlly and bossy...
但你要保證不會挑剔與專橫…
...and all Monica about it.
不會像個摩妮卡
I promise.
我保證
All right,let's see.
好，讓我看看
Now,some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
你們有一些會被剪掉 有些不會
But I promise,none of you will feel a thing.
但我保證絕對不會痛
-That's it. I quit. -What? I didn't say anything!
我不幹了 我什麼都沒說！
But this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
但這不是一張信任的表情
This is the face of a person who,you know...
這是一張，你知道的…
...doesn't trust a person.
不信任人的表情
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
對不起，對不起
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
這比我們說的要短了一點
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
你放輕鬆好嗎？ 我知道要怎麼剪
This is how he wears it.
他的髮型就是這樣
How who wears it?
誰的髮型就是這樣？
Demi Moore.
黛咪摩兒
Demi Moore is not a "he."
黛咪摩兒不是一個「他」
Well,he was a "he" in Arthur and in 10.
他在「二八佳人花公子」 與「十全十美」都是一個「他」
That's Dudley Moore!
那是杜德利摩爾！
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
我說我要像黛咪摩兒！
Oh,my God!
喔，老天！
Oh,God!
天啊！
Oh,my God! I'm sorry!
我的天，真對不起！
Which one is Demi Moore?
黛咪摩兒是哪一個？
She's the actress that was in Disclosure,Indecent Proposal,Ghost!
她是女星！演過桃色機密 桃色交易與第六感生死戀
She's got gorgeous hair.
她的頭髮非常美！
I know!
我知道！
How long do you want the cuffs?
你的袖子要多長？
At least as long as I have the pants.
至少要跟褲子一樣長久
I just got that.
我聽懂了
Now we'll do your inseam.
現在要量內縫
How is she?
她的情況如何？
It's too soon to tell.
現在還不知道
She's resting,which is a good sign.
她在休息，這是好徵兆
How's the hair?
頭髮怎麼樣？
I'm not gonna lie to you. It doesn't look good.
我不騙你 真的很不好看
I put a clip on one side,which seems to have stopped the curling.
我在一邊加上髮夾 似乎能阻止捲曲
Can we see her?
我能不能看看她？
Your hair looks too good. It'd upset her.
你的頭髮太好看了 會讓她傷心
Ross,you come on in.
羅斯，你去看看她好了
Well,how you doing?
你還好嗎？
I'm okay.
我很好
That bad,huh?
這麼糟糕？
Look,I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
我可以感覺到 女人難過脆弱的時候
It's one of my gifts.
這是我的天賦之一
Joey,when I saw him get off that plane with her...
喬伊，當我看到他 與她一起下飛機…
...I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
我以為我墜入了谷底
But today,it's like there's rock bottom...
但今天是谷底…
... 50 feet of crap...
下面還有五十尺厚的垃圾…
...then me.
…然後就是我
Tell Ross how you feel.
你必須告訴羅斯你的感受
Come on,how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
我怎麼能告訴他？ 茱莉呢？
What about her? They've only been going out for two weeks.
又怎麼樣？ 他們才在一起兩周
Ross has been in love with you for 10 years.
羅斯已經愛你十年了
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道，我不知道…
I've been with my share of women.
我交往過很多女人
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
我交往過很多別人的女人
But the point is...
但重點是…
... I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
我從來沒有對任何人 像羅斯對你這樣專情…
Really?
真的嗎？
真的？
Yo,paisan!
喂，老兄！
Can I talk to you for a sec?
我能跟你談一下嗎？
Your tailor...
你的裁縫…
...is a very bad man!
是個大壞蛋！
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
Hey,what's going on?
怎麼樣？
Joey's tailor...
喬伊的裁縫…
...took advantage of me.
吃了我的豆腐
No way! I've been going to the guy for 1 2 years.
不可能！我去他那裡十二年了
He said he was gonna do my inseam.
他說要量我的內縫
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite
他的手沿著我的腿往上摸 然後就…
What?
什麼？
Cupping.
包住了
That's how they do pants!
他們就是這樣量褲子的！
First they go up one side, they move it over.
首先量一邊 把小弟弟推到一旁
Then they go up the other side, move it back,then they do the rear.
然後量另一邊 把小弟弟推回來，然後量後面
Ross,tell him. Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
羅斯，告訴他 裁縫量褲子不都是這樣？
Yes,yes,it is. In prison!
是的，的確是這樣 在監獄裡！
What's the matter with you?
你是怎麼搞的？
What?
什麼？
That's not?
不是這樣？
Oh,my God!
我的老天！
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
就算是瑪麗泰勒摩爾 也比這個要好
I like it.
我喜歡
I do. I think it's a 10!
真的，我覺得「十全十美」！
Thank you.
謝謝
My hair is very amused.
我的頭髮很讓人開懷
Come on,things could be worse.
事情還可能更糟
You could "get caught between the moon and New York City.
你可能會被「困在紐約月光中」 （電影主題曲）
I know it's crazy,but it's true."
我知道很瘋狂，不過千真萬確 （電影主題曲）
Thank you.
謝謝
Well,I gotta go. Bye.
我要走了，待會見
Bye,Rach!
瑞秋，再見！
Wait,are you leaving?
慢著，你要走了？
That's what I meant by "bye."
所以我才說再見
Can I talk to you for a sec?
我能不能跟你說一下話？
When the doctor does that hernia test....
當醫生檢查疝氣時…
That's okay.
那樣做就沒有關係
What's going on?
怎麼啦？
Well,okay,first of all...
首先…
... Paolo and I are not back together.
波洛與我沒有在一起
That was a stupid thing I did.
那是我幹的一件蠢事
If I could go back in time and do it again...
如果我能使時光倒轉…
...well,I wouldn't.
我絕對不會這麼做
Second of all....
其次…
Is this one of those things where you break up with a guy...
我要先問清楚 這是不是當你與男友分手…
... I tell you what I think...
我告訴你我的想法…
...and the next day you get back together with him...
然後第二天你又重修舊好…
...and I look like a complete idiot?
我變成一個大蠢蛋？
Well,then,I think the guy's scum.
好，我覺得他實在很爛
I hate him. I mean,I actually I physically hate him.
我恨死他了 我真的很厭惡他
I always have.
我一直很厭惡他
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
你值得更好的男人
Really?
真的？
You deserve to be with someone who appreciates you...
你值得一個真正能欣賞你的人
...and who gets how funny...
瞭解你有多麼幽默…
...and sweet and amazing...
多麼溫柔，多麼體帖…
...and adorable and sexy you are.
多麼美麗性感…
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking:
每天早上醒來都會想著…
"Oh,my God. I'm with Rachel!"
天啊，我跟瑞秋在一起！
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
這個人能讓你感覺非常好
Like the way I do with Julie.
就像我與茱莉一樣
Was there a "second of all"?
你還沒說完？
No,I think that was the whole "all."
不，我想這就是了
I gotta go.
我要走了
Thanks.
謝謝
No,I swear to God,Dad!
不，我向天發誓，爸！
That's not how they measure pants!
不是這樣子量褲子的！
I was thinking of doing it shorter, like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
我想要剪個短髮 就像安蒂麥道威爾的髮型
-Yeah,I could do that. -Really?
這我會剪 真的？
-You wanna do it now? -Great!
你要現在就剪嗎？ 太好了！
See you.
待會見
I just wanna make really sure this time.
這次我要弄清楚
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral,right?
安蒂麥道威爾就是演 「你是我今生的新娘」？
No.
不是
That's Roddy McDowall.
那是魯迪麥道威爾
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
安蒂麥道威爾是演 「浩劫餘生」的那個傢伙
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
謝謝 別客氣